Guide to the Zaki Nusseibeh Collection of photographs AD.MC.020
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Sheikh Zayed with Somali President Siyaad Barre, Zaki Nusseibeh (far left, holding a cigarette) and Sheikh Ahmed Bin Hamid Al Qubaisi., Circa 1970; ref117; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Political Leadership; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Regional/National Dress; Cigarettes; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Siyaad Barre, Maxamed, 1920-1995
- Sheikh Zayed sitting at a coffee table with Somali President Siyaad Barre, Sheikh Ahmed Bin Hamid Al Qubaisi and Zaki Nusseibeh (right side of the couch)., Circa 1970; ref118; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Political Leadership; Furnishings; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Regional/National Dress; Food; Drinks/Beverages; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Siyaad Barre, Maxamed, 1920-1995
- Sheikh Zayed walking with Chad President Ngarta Tombalbaye, with Zaki Nusseibeh in the background., Circa 1970; ref119; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Political Leadership; Furnishings; Individual Portraits; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Tombalbaye, Ngarta, 1918-1975
- Sheikh Zayed with Archbishop President Makarios of Cyprus and Zaki Nusseibeh (far right)., 1975; ref120; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Priests/Clergymen; Furnishings; Orthodox Christianity; Political Leadership; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Makarios III, Archbishop of Cyprus, 1913-1977
- Sheikh Zayed shaking hands with Archbishop President Makarios of Cyprus, with Zaki Nusseibeh in the center., 1975; ref121; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Priests/Clergymen; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Regional/National Dress; Outdoors; Orthodox Christianity; Medals/Insignia; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Makarios III, Archbishop of Cyprus, 1913-1977
- Indira Gandhi at a press conference with Zaki Nusseibeh (far right)., Circa 1970; ref122; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; India; Political Leadership; Men; Women; Microphones; Regional/National Dress; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Radios; Furnishings; Group Portraits; Gandhi, Indira (Priyadarshini), 1917-1984
- Sheikh Zayed and Zaki Nusseibeh (left of Sheikh Zayed) walking with a group in front of the Southern Gate of Taj Mahal., Circa 1970; ref123; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Agra, India; Men; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Microphones; Political Leadership; Outdoors; Monuments/Memorials; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- A group portrait of the UAE and USA delegations with Sheikh Khalifa bin Zayed Al Nahyan, Sheikh Mohammad, Zaki Nusseibeh (left, at desk) and President Bill Clinton in the Oval Office at the Whitehouse., Circa 2000; ref124; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Washington D.C., USA; United States of America; Political Leadership; Color Photography; Regional/National Dress; Furnishings; Offices; Men; Paintings; Art; Group Portraits; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Khalifa bin Zayed bin Khalifa Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1948-2022; Clinton, Bill ((William Jefferson)), 1946-; Mohamed bin Zayed Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1961-
- An overhead view of Sheikh Zayed with French President Valéry Giscard d'Estaing at a gathering of officials., 1975; ref125; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Tapestry; Audiences/Spectators; Paris, France; Political Leadership; Men; Microphones; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Regional/National Dress; Art; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Giscard d'Estaing, Valéry, 1926-2020
- Sheikh Zayed walking with French President Valéry Giscard d'Estaing and Zaki Nusseibeh (center)., 1975; ref126; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Paris, France; Men; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Political Leadership; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Giscard d'Estaing, Valéry, 1926-2020
- Sheikh Zayed and Zaki Nusseibeh (far right) walking with Shah Mohammad Reza Pahlavi, Shah of Iran in front of Azadi Tower., Circa 1970; ref127; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Cameras; Political Leadership; Regional/National Dress; Monuments/Memorials; Tehran, Iran; Outdoors; Hats; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Mohammad Reza Pahlavi, Shah of Iran, 1919-1980
- Sheikh Zayed and Zaki Nusseibeh (right of Sheikh Zayed) walking with Shah Mohammad Reza Pahlavi, Shah of Iran in front of Azadi Tower., Circa 1970; ref128; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Monuments/Memorials; Men; Political Leadership; Canes/Walking Sticks; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Tehran, Iran; Outdoors; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Mohammad Reza Pahlavi, Shah of Iran, 1919-1980
- Sheikh Zayed with Yasser Arafat, Bruno Kreisky and Zaki Nusseibeh (far right)., Circa 1970; ref129; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Political Leadership; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Furnishings; Art; Paintings; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Telephones; Political Leadership; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Kreisky, Bruno, 1911-1990; Arafat, Yasser ((Mohammed Abdel Rahman Abdel Raouf Arafat al-Qudwa al-Husseini)), 1929-2004
- Sheikh Zayed with Yasser Arafat, Bruno Kreisky and Zaki Nusseibeh (far right)., 1981; ref130; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Regional/National Dress; Furnishings; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Art; Paintings; Telephones; Political Leadership; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Kreisky, Bruno, 1911-1990; Arafat, Yasser ((Mohammed Abdel Rahman Abdel Raouf Arafat al-Qudwa al-Husseini)), 1929-2004
- Sheikh Zayed and a group of people at the Great Wall of China., May 1990; ref131; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Flags; Color Photography; China; Men; Women; Crowds; Monuments/Memorials; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Outdoors; Political Leadership; Medals/Insignia; Facial Hair; Group Portraits; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Sheikh Zayed with Emperor Akihito Emeritus of Japan and Zaki Nusseibeh (second from the right)., May 1990; ref132; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Tokyo, Japan; Color Photography; Men; Paintings; Furnishings; Political Leadership; Art; Regional/National Dress; Bow Ties; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Akihito, Emperor Emeritus of Japan, 1933-; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Sheikh Zayed shaking hands with Nelson Mandela on a state visit with Sultan bin Zayed Al Nahyan and Zaki Nusseibeh (left, wearing a suit)., 1995; ref133; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Color Photography; Political Leadership; Flags; Regional/National Dress; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Outdoors; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Mandela, Nelson, 1918-2013
- A group portrait of the rulers of the United Arab Emirates. Sheikh Mohammed, Sheikh Khalifa bin Zayed Al Nahyan, Sheikh Sultan, Sheikh Hamdan, Sheikh Mansour, Sheikh Abdullah, Sheikh Saif, Sheikh Ahmed, Sheikh Saeed, Sheikh Falah, Sheikh Nasser, Sheikh Nahyan, Sheikh Issa, Sheikh Hazza, Sheikh Tahnoon., Circa 1970; ref134; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Color Photography; Men; Group Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Canes/Walking Sticks; Furnishings; Carpets/Rugs; Political Leadership; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Khalifa bin Zayed bin Khalifa Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1948-2022; Sultan bin Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1953-2019; Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, Sheikh, 1949-; Sheikh, Hamdan bin Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, 1963-
- Sheikh Zayed walking with Nelson Mandela on a red carpet with Zaki Nusseibeh (center)., 1995; ref135; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Color Photography; Political Leadership; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Men; Regional/National Dress; Outdoors; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Mandela, Nelson, 1918-2013
- Sheikh Zayed and Nelson Mandela receiving gifts from Emirati girls with Zaki Nusseibeh (center)., 1995; ref136; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Color Photography; Men; Women; Girls; Regional/National Dress; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Airplanes; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Jewelry; Transportation; Political Leadership; Outdoors; Children; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Mandela, Nelson, 1918-2013
- Sheikh Zayed shaking hands with Nelson Mandela with Zaki Nusseibeh in the background., 1995; ref137; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Color Photography; Political Leadership; Flags; Men; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Outdoors; Group Portraits; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Mandela, Nelson, 1918-2013
- Sheikh Zayed at a ribbon cutting ceremony., Circa 1970; ref138; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Color Photography; Ceremonies; Men; Crowds; Flags; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Political Leadership; Individual Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Sheikh Zayed waving in front of the entrance of a plane with Zaki Nusseibeh on the left, facing the camera., Circa 1970; ref139; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Airplanes; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Regional/National Dress; Transportation; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Political Leadership; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Sheikh Ahmed bin Hamid Al-Qubaisi walking with Zaki Nusseibeh (left of Sheikh Zayed) in front of Temple of Jupiter in Baalbek, Lebanon., Circa 1970; ref140; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Baalbek, Lebanon; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Regional/National Dress; Outdoors; Monuments/Memorials; Religious Sites; Architecture; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Political Leadership
- Sheikh Zayed with British officials seated among a crowd watching an eagle with Sheikh Sultan bin Zayed Al Nahyan, Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, and Zaki Nusseibeh (leaning forward between Sheikh Zayed and a British official)., Circa 1990; ref141; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Political Leadership; England, UK; Men; Animals; Birds; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Color Photography; Regional/National Dress; Political Leadership; Outdoors; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Sultan bin Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1953-2019; Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, Sheikh, 1949-
- Sheikh Khalifa bin Zayed Al Nahyan with French President Jacques Chirac and Zaki Nusseibeh (left) in front of a falcon statue in Palais de L'Elysée., 21 July 2006; ref142; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Furnishings; Paris, France; Palaces; Color Photography; Men; Political Leadership; Statues/Sculptures; Animals; Birds; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Paintings; Statues/Sculptures; Art; Palaces; Group Portraits; Royalty; Chirac, Jacques, 1932-2019; Khalifa bin Zayed bin Khalifa Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1948-2022
- Sheikh Khalifa bin Zayed Al Nahyan shaking hands with Zaki Nusseibeh (left) next to policemen., Circa 2000; ref143; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Police; Uniforms; Color Photography; Regional/National Dress; Political Leadership; Group Portraits; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair; Royalty; Khalifa bin Zayed bin Khalifa Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1948-2022
- Sheikh Zayed and Zaki Nusseibeh (right of Sheikh Zayed) during a a visit to Westminister with Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, Sheikh Sultan bin Zayed Al Nahyan, Sheikh Mohammed bin Zayed Al Nahyan., 1989; ref144; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; London, England, UK; Color Photography; Men; Churches; Priests/Clergymen; Architecture; Regional/National Dress; Military/Soldiers; Chandeliers; Religious Sites; Uniforms; Political Leadership; Group Portraits; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Sultan bin Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1953-2019; Mohamed bin Zayed Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1961-; Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, Sheikh, 1949-
- Sheikh Zayed in the City of London Hall with Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, Sheikh Sultan bin Zayed Al Nahyan, Sheikh Mohammed bin Zayed Al Nahyan, and Zaki Nusseibeh (behind Sheikh Zayed's throne)., 1989; ref145; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; London, England, UK; Color Photography; Swords/Knives; Flags; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Men; Women; Royalty; Armor; Military/Soldiers; Political Leadership; Swords/Knives; Medals/Insignia; Carpets/Rugs; Weapons; Political Leadership; Furnishings; Group Portraits; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004; Mohamed bin Zayed Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1961-; Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, Sheikh, 1949-; Sultan bin Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1953-2019
- Sheikh Zayed walking through Souq Al Markezi (central market)., Circa 1970; ref146; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Markets; Men; Military/Soldiers; Street Vendors; Regional/National Dress; Uniforms; Political Leadership; Food; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Sheikh Zayed walking with a crowd and waving at Souq Al Markezi (central market)., Circa 1970; ref147; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Police; Crowds; Markets; Cars/Trucks; Regional/National Dress; Transportation; Buildings; Political Leadership; Outdoors; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Sheikh Zayed looking at a fabric swatch book at Souq Al Markezi (central market)., Circa 1970; ref148; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Markets; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Regional/National Dress; Shops; Hats; Political Leadership; Medals/Insignia; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004
- Sheikh Zayed walking with a crowd at Souq Al Markezi (central market)., Circa 1970; ref149; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Markets; Men; Crowds; Military/Soldiers; Guns; Street Vendors; Uniforms; Regional/National Dress; Regional/National Dress; Weapons; Buildings; Shops; Political Leadership; Outdoors; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Royalty; Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan, Sheikh, 1918-2004